[opening theme playing]
LECTURE HALL
[man] Young-joo,
I have something to tell you.
I've been watching you
and thinking about you
for a long time now
and I've...
been wanting
to ask you...
will you go out with me?
Huh, Young-joo?
[murmuring]
[Jae-yoon] What's this? What's going on.
Hey, what's this deal?
He's confessing his love to Young-joo.
- Young-joo?
- Here we go again.
He can't do this to her.
Let him do whatever. Who cares anyway?
She's very pretty.
Um, see, the thing is,
lately I feel more like being single.
[cries]
[sighs]
Why is everyone crazy over that girl, huh?
[sighs] A bunch of crazy people.
[professor] For the next project,
you work in pairs. You have three weeks.
- Then we'll begin presentations.
- [all groan]
Take the rest of this hour and decide
who you'll be partnering up with.
I look forward to seeing your work.
- [students] Yes, sir.
- That's it for today.
[together] Thank you.
- [Hyun-soo] Let's go to the lounge.
- [Jae-yoon] Sure.
This asshole teacher really needs
to be locked up or something.
- When are you free?
- [Hyun-soo] Whenever, man.
Next week? That work?
Yeah. Oh, except Wednesday.
Hey, Jae-yoon.
Huh?
Care to team up with me?
You and I?
No, thank you.
I already paired up with him.
- Oh.
- Yeah.
Uh, okay.
Young-joo, why not pair up with me?
I'm leaving him.
You asshole! Are you serious right now?
Come on, Young-joo. I'm not gonna
work with him. I insist.
Uh...
Thank you, Hyung-soo.
I'll text you later, okay?
Sure.
Look out for my texts.
Can I kill you?
[students chattering]
Wow.
You're really throwing away
a ten year friendship for a girl.
[scoffs] You're a piece of shit.
It's not just any girl.
It's Kang Young-joo.
Goddess of engineering.
"It's Kang Young-joo.
Goddess of engineering."
- That's why I paid for your meal, dumbass.
- Fucking asshole.
But, I mean...
Why pick you?
What was that?
Didn't you even wonder why?
Why Young-joo would want you
to be her partner.
It's not obvious?
It's these looks.
My aura is pure charisma.
That's utter bull.
How did you get so lucky?
- Oh, shit.
- [thuds]
Oh...
Jesus.
You should've agreed to do the assignment.
Why should I?
Why wouldn't you?
She's the coolest girl in our class.
She's not all that special, really.
- Don't you think she's pretty?
- Not one little bit.
- She's not attractive at all.
- Your eyes are fucked.
- You went to an all-boys school, so--
- Hey, what the hell?
- You're a damn loner!
- You're an asshole.
You're an asshole.
I'm not a loner.
- [Hyun-soo] Yeah, you are.
- I had a girlfriend.
- Really? When?
- Back in elementary school.
Everyone knows
elementary school-- [exclaims]
- [both exclaim]
- That scared me.
What are you doing there?
Why? Can't I be here?
I thought any
mechanical engineering student
was allowed to use this lounge, no?
You really shouldn't gossip
behind somebody's back, asshole.
You're the one gossiping asshole.
Young-joo, I'll text you!
Did she catch that?
- You really overdid it this time.
- Did I?
Yeah, you did. What did I do?
- Welcome aboard.
- It's a pleasure to work here.
- Great. Don't let me down.
- Thanks.
Let me introduce you to your new mentor.
[suspenseful music playing]
Hello, Lee Jae-yoon.
Do you know each other?
That's such great news! [chuckles]
- Teach him well, Young-joo.
- Yeah.
- I'll use Spartan methods to train him.
- [chuckles]
Best of luck.
Later.
Welcome, Jae-yoon.
Is this your first time selling ice cream?
Your not so pretty, unattractive mentor
will make sure
that you learn all the details.
[chuckles]
She heard...
everything.
You see what I sent you?
[woman chuckling] What the hell is this?
Dude, it's ridiculous, right?
[woman] Totally.
I mean, I never thought
I'd hear this kind of bullshit.
For the past 22 years,
my looks have been everything.
Am I not really cute?
He doesn't find me attractive at all.
It's me Kang Young-joo.
If he thinks he's better looking,
his fish face needs a mirror.
[woman] Hey, hey.
That's a bit harsh, don't you think?
[Young-joo] Not at all.
He started at first.
When I see him tomorrow,
that's when the real revenge begins.
[woman] Hello? Hey Kang Young-joo?
Hello? What is it?
[screams]
Jeez, what the hell? What's with you?
I was just standing here.
What's your deal?
Hey, how come you're standing there?
"How come you're standing there?"
What? Can't I stand here?
I can. This happens
to be a public bus stop
that anyone in Korea is allowed to use.
Good evening.
Shit.
He heard...
everything.
- [man] I haven't even had a bite of this.
- [bell dings]
[man] This ice cream has melted!
Just look at it. Huh?
Look closely!
This ice cream is all mushed
and you're responsible.
Uh, sir, I just checked your receipt now
and it's been seven hours
since you purchased your ice cream.
Which is something we always tell you
when you make a purchase.
- After three hours after purchase, we're--
- Hye, miss.
Are you actually
lecturing your a customer?
Look, don't talk down to me, sir.
I'm only trying to tell you
what the rules--
Refund me. You better give me
my money back right now!
I keep telling you,
the rules don't allow any refunds--
Asshole!
[screams, whimpers]
- Hey, what...
- Disrupting business?
Destruction of property.
Defamation. Battery.
- Assault. Etcetera.
- What are you--
This is a list of all the crimes
that you just committed.
All of it's on video
and will be used as evidence.
Our corporate legal team will use it
to press charges against you.
[man] I mean- What did--
If you have a statement,
say it to the camera.
This-- This business is terrible.
[bell dings]
[sighs] Damn.
Freaking asshole man.
- I guess I should say thank you.
- Whatever.
Hey,
are you studying a double major
in law or what?
I saw somebody on a TV show say it.
But I didn't think that
it was really gonna work.
Oh, yeah? Tell me the name of that show.
No, actually, it's an awful show. Skip it.
Mmm... Okay.
Okay.
Hey, what I said about you...
Sorry. For the things
I said the other night.
You are?
Really?
Hey, don't worry about it. I'm joking.
I was talking bad about you too, you know?
So we're even.
[chuckles] Yeah!
That's right, you asshole.
You did it first.
Yeah. I just said you were unattractive.
But you called me a fish.
- Yeah but I said--
- Do I look fishy to you?
Flounder. Halibut. Which one?
I don't know. Sorry.
I was rude.
I heard humans evolve from fish,
so I guess I am one.
I'll wash your rag.
[gasps] I can't believe you right now.
[sighs]
My favorite expert
in this particular field
is Professor Herr, who researches at MIT.
He's, without a doubt, one of the leading
voices in the field of biometrics.
[professor muffled]
[gasps]
Aw, shit. My God, he's stunning.
It's very popular and everyone loves it.
Over there we have...
[romantic music playing]
[woman] What was that?
It's...
delicious.
[chuckles softly]
Yeah, this is normal.
This is it.
[chuckles]
[brakes squeak]
- See you later.
- Have a good night.
Good evening.
So long.
[romantic music playing]
Aw, shit.
LEE JAE-YOON
[romantic music playing]
Ah!
Ahh! No, no!
No! How is it possible?
[screaming]
- [Young-joo's mother] Dinner's ready.
- I'm not hungry!
[Young-joo] This one's for you.
And this one's for you, sir.
Oh! You really shouldn't have.
- Thank you, Young-joo.
- Thank you, Young-joo. This is great.
Merry Christmas.
What about Jae-yoon?
[gasps]
Oh, that's right. I only brought in two.
[smacks] Ah, hold on!
- There's this one.
- [chuckles]
Lee Jae-yoon.
This gift's for you.
[chuckling]
I run pretty warm.
So I avoid using scarves
because I tend to overheat.
Just give it to somebody else.
Sir, the outside as well? I'll do it now.
Wrong way. Ugh, it's hot.
[shuddering]
He actually turned down my scarf?
Oh, my gosh!
[sighs] You scared me.
Lee Jae-yoon, what is wrong with you, huh?
- Hmm?
- Do you know why I want you to have this?
Not really
I made this because I...
wanted to do something nice for you.
I knitted a scarf by myself.
Yeah?
Young-joo, I just...
[sighs] I'm sorry.
I don't think I would...
- ever really use the scarf, you know.
- Huh?
Sorry,
Uh... Ah... Oh... Yeah.
[chuckles] That's understandable.
It's okay.
Let's go.
Hello. Welcome. Which one's a good flavor?
Well, right now we have
the almond and caramel bonbons.
These are selling really well
at the moment.
They're our newest flavor. Yum.
So there's this really fun one
we've called Rainbow Watermelon.
This one's also a new flavor,
so a lot of customers
are currently trying it.
[man] Cool. I like those sweet flavors.
But if you prefer
an even sweeter option...
- Yeah.
- ...then I recommend my favorite,
which is the Giant Chocolate Puzzle.
- You should try it.
- [man] Okay.
That's the one we make...
So are you dating Young-joo or--
What are you saying? No way, dude!
It's not like that.
Really?
There's still a chance. [laughs]
[laughs]
Hey...
not to be rude, however,
are you really in a position
to turn her down, like--
There you go talking weird again
Seriously, stop it.
It was just a question. My bad.
Ugh!
Well, you aren't completely wrong,
you know.
Huh?
[sighs]
In what scenario would a girl like her
date me, really?
Impossible. Huh?
- Right?
- [sighs]
- [sobbing]
- [man] Hey!
Why are you crying?
[manager] Young-joo, are you okay?
- I'm okay. [sobbing]
- What--
All I did was ask
for an almond caramel bonbon.
No, no, no. It really isn't your fault.
Sir, I'm really not feeling well.
May I be excused?
[manager] Oh, yes. Please go home.
[sobbing]
Young-joo, it's okay. We'll handle it.
Young-joo, I--
[bell dings]
[engine whirring]
[sniffling, sobbing]
Shit! This sucks.
Oh, so embarrassing.
[crying]
Young-joo, I was actually thinking...
- about what I said earlier.
- God damn it!
Hey, hold on!
Hey, Young-joo, hold on.
- [screams]
- Hey! Whoa, whoa!
- [cries] It's so freaking annoying.
- You okay?
- Young-joo.
- It's always getting undone! [cries]
Wait, what?
God damn it! This freaking shoelace
is always undone!
The shoelace?
You should have told me.
I could have taught you.
I'm actually quite skilled
in tying shoelaces.
Really?
[Jae-yoon] Of course.
Look, just like this.
This goes through here...
and then...
Am I really that bad?
[Jae-yoon] Not bad.
You're beautiful.
Hey, Jae-yoon, you asshole!
It did come undone.
You're very relaxed, huh?
Young-joo, please, just get
it together and hurry up!
[panting]
Lee Jae-yoon and In-ho.
- Yes, sir.
- Private Ra In-ho.
What can we do?
It's over, right?
[gasps]
[growling]
[both exclaim]
[exclaiming]
- What the fuck?
- Get it together!
Fuck! Fuck!
What the fuck is that thing?
[snarling]
[guns cocking]
What do we do?
[Jae-yoon] Get back!
[exclaiming]
- [snarling]
- [screaming]
- Ahh!
- [snarls]
- [In-ho] Corporal Jeon Hyung-bae!
- [clangs]
- [snarling]
- [screaming]
Kim Young-man, shoot!
[grunts]
[screaming]
[clanging]
[Tae-hwa] Shoot it now!
I'm so sorry for this.
[gunshot]
Quickly. Let's go.
[exclaims]
God damn it.
Are you okay?
[Jin-wook] Look.
Please, help me.
No, no, no! No! No! I'm not infected.
Wait, hold up!
If he can talk, then maybe it's true.
Let's not kill him yet.
[man] Fucking hell!
If you wanna kill me, do it.
Did you get bitten by a zombie?
- I got bitten, man.
- [Tae-shik] Hey!
I got bitten and that's why
I have this shit.
On top of that,
you're all trying to smack me?
That's mean, dude.
Just go.
You're all just a bunch of assholes.
Go fuck yourselves!
Look, he's slurring his words.
He's too far gone to be a zombie.
- Let's go now.
Hey, are you guys really
gonna leave me here?
Help me! Help me!
I don't wanna die.
Oh, a Yoon Jong-shin fanatic.
- Please, help me.
- What?
Can't he come with us?
- No way!
- I'm begging you to save me.
- Please. Just this once.
- Does it really hurt?
Have you gone completely insane?
If you're too scared then go!
You serious?
Why are you talking to me like that?
You said I could be less formal
when eating.
So that's me being casual.
You don't like it?
Then leave, Seo Jin-wook.
[mobile ringing]
Hang up! Hang up!
- Turn it off! Where is it?
- [grunting]
- Yoon Jong-shin!
- Sorry. I was supposed to be studying--
- [all] Shh!
- [snarling]
Ah, shit! I told you to leave the guy.
This way. Let's get out of here!
- [man] Let's go!
- [Young-joo screams]
[Tae-shik] This way!
- [snarling]
- [screaming]
[snarling]
- [gunshot]
- Ahh! [pants]
[thuds]
[Gye-young] Soo-jeong.
Hyung-bae.
[whimpers]
What were you thinking shooting a gun?
It's reckless and it's prohibited!
I'm sorry...
- Apologies.
- Sir!
If Soo-jeong hadn't acted,
In-Ho would have died.
Kwak Gye-young, know your damn place!
You all get your shit together!
- Kwak Gye-young.
- Sir.
Take her to the living quarters.
Take care of Hyung-bae.
Remove the bodies immediately.
- Get to it!
- Yes, sir.
[all] Yes, sir.
- Come on.
Please take this.
- Commander...
- It's safer inside.
Park Sung-wook, are you listening to me?
- Yeah.
- I'll report this to the brigade.
Get your shit together, Commander.
Yes. Thanks you're right.
I think I'll rest inside for a while.
[coughing]
Cover him.
[snarling]
[Young-joo] Oh.
They're really going at it.
Hold up. Go in.
Hey, I'm sorry.
But if you wanna join us,
we have no choice
...but to tie you up.
If he makes it.
Makes it?
If he can make it any longer, you know?
Look how his eyes are getting red.
He's transforming.
[mumbling]
Any ideas on what to do?
- Murder him?
- [mumbling and whimpering]
He's gonna turn into a zombie right now!
[mumbling and whimpering]
Oh, you want us to pity you, you asshole?
[sighs] That's why I tied up
his mouth and his hands.
Young-joo, don't pretend to be nice.
- I mean, seriously.
- Jin-wook!
- [Tripeater mumbling]
- "Don't pretend"? That's a little harsh.
- Huh? Then what should I say? "Fuck"?
- [Tripeater sobbing]
Let me tell you, if it weren't for her,
none of this would be h--
- Hey!
- [Tae-shik] Relax, man.
Young-joo, you need to stop this now.
- Okay?
- You son of a bitch! What's your deal?
- I'll smash your face in, you zombie!
- [Tae-shik] Stop.
- Son of a-- [grunts]
- [vomits]
[gagging]
[Jin-wook grunts]
- [Young-joo groans]
- Let's untie him. Yeah?
If something happens,
it's not my fault, okay?
[gagging]
- [vomiting]
- [all groaning]
[Young-joo] Dude, how much did you drink?
[Tripeater inhales deeply]
There was the Chinese restaurant.
- Two bottles of soju.
- [sighs]
And then there's
the bottles at Hangang Park.
- [sighs]
- And then...
another bottle
- at the restaurant for the hangover.
- What the hell?
- [zombie snarling and growling]
- [screaming]
I had something else.
What did I eat?
Just look down and you'll find out.
You ate some fried rice.
Water. Water, please, guys.
[chuckles] You failed finals three times
and went drinking instead of studying?
- Are you going for a fourth time?
- Whoa.
A fourth time?
Don't you dare say such horrible things.
If I fail a fourth time,
I'll have to join the army.
I had a drink to take the edge off.
- That's all.
- [Young-joo sighs]
Bring the water.
- [Tripeater] Water.
- Wait, me?
Come on. Go get it.
[sighs] Sure thing. Anything at all.
- Why don't you give him one more drink?
- If I may interject...
I might have a couple theories.
- [Young-joo screams]
- [zombie growling]
[Young-joo and Tripeater screaming]
- [gasps and whimpers]
- [Young-joo groans]
- [zombie snarling]
- [gasps]
- [yelling]
- [zombie snarling]
- [Young-joo yelling]
- [thuds]
- [zombie snarling]
[splattering]
[whimpering]
- [gasps]
- Wait, wait, wait.
[quirky music playing]
- [blows air]
- [breathalyzer beeping]
[breathalyzer beeping]
- Fuck yeah!
- [Jin-wook] Jesus! He scared me.
What's wrong with him?
[panicked screaming]
[Tae-shik] Ta-da! Look at this.
- He's drunk. So what?
- You saw it, right?
You saw how that thing ran past the guy.
Uh, yeah, I think I did.
There were a bunch of them.
They went right past that guy
and ran directly for us.
Can you please
just cut to the chase and explain?
I've come to two theories.
One, if you've had a lot to drink,
the zombies won't attack you.
Two, even when bitten,
if you're drunk,
you don't turn into a zombie.
So, I think getting wasted
is our best option.
- [chuckles] Well...
- Wasted?
- For Christ's sake.
- [Young-joo] That sounds dumb.
Then how do you explain this guy, huh?
It's just a theory,
but what else have we got?
- [panicked screaming]
- We should start drinking now.
- What?
- How much should we drink?
- [Tae-shik] This much.
- [gasps]
[Jin-wook] Wow. That's...
How you end up like that?
Why are you looking at me?
I'm so offended.
I'm a drunk too, and I admit it.
I'd rather go out when it's light out,
So let's drink till morning.
Okay? Let's drink.
[Jin-wook] Let's drink.
[Tripeater] Will you give me
a bottle too, right?
Please? Please, I...
- Shit.
- [line ringing]
[Tripeater] I wanna drink too.
[Tripeater moans]
[automated voice] I'm sorry.
- The number you are trying to reach...
- [Tripeater] So thirsty.
JAE-YOON
[Young-joo] Jae-yoon,
I'm hiding in a restaurant
that's very close to Tower A.
If you see this, please call me.
[mellow music playing]
[Tae-shik] Ta-da. Bottoms up.
- [sighs]
- [Tripeater] Sir, I'd like one too.
Sir?
[friend 1] Don't cry, Young-joo.
Thanks for being here.
Please, eat.
[indistinct chatter]
- [friend 2] You should eat too.
- [Young-joo] I'm not hungry.
- [Jae-yoon] Are you crying?
- Oh, my God. [chuckles]
- [Jae-yoon chuckles]
- I'm not.
- Smile. Come on, smile.
- Hey! [chuckles]
Seriously. [chuckles]
- Aren't you tired?
- Not at all.
- I want to say thank you.
- No need. I'll always be here.
[music continues playing]
A present from my father.
[sighs]
He really didn't have
to leave me anything.
- [chuckles] Thank you, sir.
- [chuckles]
I thought you knew I didn't smoke though.
- Huh?
- Hey, my dad didn't smoke either.
- [chuckles]
That's true.
Hey, I saw him carrying this around,
but I never actually saw him
smoking a cigarette.
This is...
what I gifted my dad when I was younger
using my allowance.
Since then, he always carried it around,
protecting it like some prized possession.
Whenever he'd see me,
he'd pretend to smoke a cigarette.
[chuckles] It always brightened my day.
[chuckles and sniffles]
[sucks]
[inhales through mouth]
- [blows air]
- [chuckles]
Stop that. [chuckles]
- What a smoke. So good.
- Cut it out.
[gasps]
Young-joo.
[groans softly]
[sighs]
[slow music playing]
NAME: LEE JAE-YOON
POSITION: SHINGUNG ASSISTANT
[sighs]
[siren wailing distantly]
[sniffles]
[tapping keys]
[line ringing]
- [line disconnects]
- [sighs]
YOUNG-JOO, MY LOVE
[sighs]
[softly] Fuck.
[Sung-wook panting]
[solemn music playing]
Oh, shit.
[panting]
[grunts]
[breath trembling]
[sobbing]
Oh, shit.
[Seon-mi] The country
is in a state of turmoil today
as continued attacks
have left the population anxious
and fearful for their lives.
What we know so far
is that these zombie perpetrators
assault indiscriminately
for no known reason.
The monsters have been witnessed
striking victims from all directions,
killing them
through bites to their bodies.
The government has suspended
all public transportation,
including subways and busses.
It is imperative for the safety
of the general public
that people stay at home,
avoid going out at all costs,
regardless of the circumstances.
[reporter] Yes. We'll continue
to monitor and report the situation.
[man on TV] No birds? No iron.
The movement is revolutionary. MOTY.
[sighs]
Private Ra In-ho!
Am I allowed to speak my mind?
Hey, dumbass. Dude, read the room.
What is it? Say it.
There's got to be a reason why yesterday,
Private first class Che Chul-Woo,
didn't actually turn into a zombie
right away after he was bitten.
What do you think it is?
There's a chance it was something
he ate that slowed it down,
and that...
I got a feeling
that thing is this ginseng liquid
that Chul-Woo always had on him.
What if this is
what slowed down the infection?
[quirky music playing]
[clicks tongue]
[Gye-young] What
are you talking about, idiot?
Don't just make stuff up.
Private Ra In-ho,
you're incredibly out of line.
[Gye-young] Huh? [gasps]
The way you talk...
What about the way I'm talking?
You talk like a soldier.
I'm trying.
So? What?
I have a personal question for you.
Uh, what is it?
How did a civilian like you
learn to shoot that way?
- [Gye-young] Oh...
- Oh...
I was surprised too.
Who taught you to shoot?
Well...
Actually, it's a secret. [chuckles softly]
I was a competitive shooter
until high school.
- National Guard.
- What? Seriously though?
- Wow! Oh, that makes sense.
- [chuckles]
Whoa.
- [gunshot]
- [all gasp]
[intriguing music playing]
What was it?
What was that?
- [Young-man] Shit. Come on.
- [In-ho] Wait for me.
What's going on?
Where was it?
Where'd the shots come from?
The situation room.
- The situation room!
- The Commander?
I think he's held up in the office.
[Gye-young and Jae-yoon gasp]
- Aw, shit.
- Oh, no. [whimpers]
- Let's go. Come on.
- No, wait, wait.
WAR ROOM
[Young-man] Sir, be careful.
[suspenseful music playing]
Shit, why are we doing this?
- Wait!
- [In-ho yelps]
[breath trembling]
1ST PLATOON DUTY ROSTER
LIVE AS A SHIELD! DIE IN LOYALTY!
[mysterious music playing]
FIRST LIEUTENANT PARK SUNG-WOOK
RETURN TO BRIGADE
[Tripeater] If I manage to get a .209...
- [Young-joo] I got it.
- [Tripeater] You did?
- ...209?
- [Young-joo] I got it.
- I got it.
- [Tripeater] You sure?
- You got it.
- [Young-joo cheering]
- You got it. You got it.
- [laughing]
- [Young-joo] I got it.
- [Tripeater] You got it. You got it.
- [Young-joo] Amazing.
- [Tripeater] Well done.
- Wow, I feel great.
- [Young-joo groans]
I'm so drunk. Wasted...
Completely shitfaced.
[Young-joo groans]
[sighs]
[drunkenly] Idiot.
Ah...
So you pretended to be
strong and independent,
but you can't keep up with us. [chuckles]
[Tripeater] Can you untie me, please?
I have the highest blood alcohol level
out of all of you. [hiccups]
- Should I?
- Absolutely not.
- We can't.
- I'm sorry, bro.
When in the hell will you untie him?
Just... The sun's already up.
If we get drunk like this,
won't it be harder
to deal with the zombies?
Hey, nothing's easy.
[Tae-shik] Young-joo.
Our goal is Tower A.
We're going.
Why in the hell are you going to Tower A?
- What's your boyfriend got to do with it?
- Hey!
- Do you want to repeat a fourth time?
- Young-joo! [hiccups]
Look...
all of us have to go over to Tower A,
so we can meet up
with the soldiers and be safer.
And be with Jae-yoon.
Correct.
And your Private Jae-yoon is there.
He'll save us.
I got a car too, and it's an American car.
- American car?
- Oh...
- [Tae-shik] Yes.
- American cars are awesome.
The survival kit's there too.
- Where are you going?
- Can you untie me?
[Young-joo chuckles]
[Tae-shik] You're too wasted.
- Let's go.
- Where are you...
Hey, Kang Young-joo. Wait up.
Kang Young-joo!
Hey, where you going, dude?
- Come back! Hey!
- [Young-joo] I'm free!
[Tae-shik singing] I've got a hammer...
[Jin-wook] Kang Young-joo.
[singing] Brother, I'm sorry
I can't untie those hands
My car is off-road
And it is safe
It's very safe
Where'd they go?
[solemn music playing]
[Jae-yoon] I think it's over.
[In-ho] Huh?
[sighs] There's no reason
for us to be here.
I don't understand. What?
Our service here has no use any longer.
Jae-yoon, wait. Are you...
going to desert us
and go try to find your girlfriend?
Yeah. How am I supposed to just wait here
when she could've gotten hurt
on her way to see me at the tower?
- [sighs]
- [In-ho clears throat]
I need to find Young-joo.
I have to get out of here now.
[grunts]
Then I'll go along with you.
And we'll leave together.
I have got to protect Hayul and my wife!
Yeah.
We have got to be sure
our loved ones are safe.
[sighs] Let's go.
Let's go speak with the Commander.
[In-ho] Hmm?
Wait, right now?
[zombies growling]
[Young-joo] Ah, zombies!
- Move out of the way.
- [zombies growling]
- I have to go and see Jae-yoon!
- Hey, are you crazy? Shh!
[Young-joo] Ugh...
I thought you said
zombies can't attack when you're drunk.
- Let's go.
- [groans]
- Come here. Come on.
- [Young-joo groans]
[zombies growling]
- [Jin-wook] Come on.
- [gasps]
- [Jin-wook] This way. Oh, wait, wait.
- [Young-joo groans]
- Hey, zombies!
- [Jin-wook] Hey, stop.
- Hey, come here. Hey!
- Come on, please, let's go.
- I can totally win again them.
- No, you can't win.
You will never win.
[Young-joo groans]
[panting]
[Jin-wook] Oh, fuck, we're fucked!
Fuck, we can't run away now.
We're gonna get eaten!
[Jin-wook sobbing]
[laughing]
Is that funny? Huh?
[Tripeater laughing]
Oh, gosh.
What the hell? You got scared?
Hey, you said
they can't actually bite you, right?
Go and do something about it.
Then go ahead and untie me, dude.
Are you seriously
asking that right now?
- Hey, untie him, now!
- [groans]
- Okay.
- You can just do it yourself.
I can't help all tied up like this.
- [sighs]
- Okay, I'll untie you.
Untie him. [laughing]
[Jin-wook] Here. It's off.
- [Young-joo] It's done. Yeah.
- [sighs]
[growls]
[both gasp]
[Young-joo and Tripeater laugh]
- Go, go.
- I trust you.
[quirky music playing]
[zombies growling]
- [Young-joo groans] I don't feel good.
- Shh!
[zombies growling]
[horn honks]
[mumbling]
[horn honking]
[zombies growling]
- [Jin-wook] Hey, hey. Get up.
- [Young-joo] Where are we going?
- [horn honking]
- [zombies growling]
- [Tripeater] Wait for me!
- [Young-joo] Hey, you!
- [Tripeater] Woo-hoo!
- [Young-joo] Hurry up!
[solemn music playing]
CHOI CHUL-WOO - PARK SUNG-WOOK
JEON HYUNG-BAE
SAFETY
FIRE
[breath trembling]
[sniffles and sighs]
[whimpering]
[sobbing]
[sighs]
[Jae-yoon] Privates Lee Jae-yoon
and Ra In-ho. Sir, we'd--
Oh...
[gulps]
Yeah. What's going on?
What is...
going on?
Uh, yeah.
Park Sung-wook. Um...
I was trying to... [sniffles]
Ballistics... Like... like this.
Like... like... like this... direction.
- Inspection.
- Inspection?
- Yes, that's right.
- [both] Oh.
Inspection.
I was conducting
an inspection on Park's case.
Why are you here?
Oh. Yes, sir. We're really low on food,
and our current issue is figuring out
how to successfully access
our resupply lines.
Sadly, we've got
an even bigger problem on our hands.
- Which is?
- Private In-ho, explain it to him.
Private Ra In-ho. Allow me to explain!
As you recall yesterday,
the power went out, then turned back on,
and without having any power,
we had no ATS.
Yeah, I remember yesterday.
At that point,
the hotel's electricity supply
should have switched over
from external to the backups.
Which means the only reason
that we have water
is because the water tanks are running.
So the tanks, the water and the pumps
are currently only being powered
solely by the hotel's generators.
If the generators give out,
then our water supply will also run out.
When do you think that will be?
[gulps] I would say...
we only have a few days remaining.
That's all.
[quirky music playing]
[phone ringing]
This is Master Sergeant Jung speaking.
- [man] This is Battalion commander.
- Salute.
[man] I'm sending
a resupply helicopter by noon today.
Make sure to meet us
on the roof right on arrival.
- Stand by.
- Yes.
[drums beating]
At noon,
the supply helicopter will arrive.
- What?
- [Soo-jeong] Hmm?
[Tae-hwa] The first time
we've had a heli in the compound,
but if we stay on top of it,
- we should be able to handle it.
- Shit, man.
[Tae-hwa] Remember safety first.
Everybody remain alert.
Be ready for anything.
- All right?
- [all] Yes, sir
[Tae-hwa] From now on,
leave your armor on at all times.
Gye-young, go get some more armor.
Soo-Jeong should wear it as well.
Yes, sir!
Thank you, sir!
[sighs and grunts]
[chuckles]
[sighs and groans]
[military music playing]
[soldier] Opera, this is Eagle One.
Approaching the rooftop now.
[helicopter hovering]
Bringing her down.
[Gye-young] Oh, come on. Hurry up.
[Soo-jeong] It's coming. It's coming.
[Kyung-sik] This is Opera, Opera.
Fish, respond.
Can't that thing just take me home?
- They can do that?
- [Gye-young] Should I ask?
This is Opera, Opera. Fish, respond.
[somber music playing]